twitch.com 2016-06-27

# Twitch

  1. Welcome to the web site [www.twitch.tv](http://www.twitch.tv/) , and any other web sites, applications, or services that link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, the " **Twitch Service** "), which sites, applications or services are operated or produced by Twitch Interactive, Inc. (" **Twitch** "). Twitch values the privacy of the users, subscribers, publishers, members, and others who visit and use the Twitch Service (collectively or individually, " **You** " or " **Users** ") and wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose information from and about you. 

By agreeing to this Privacy Policy in your Twitch account setup, or by using the Twitch Service, you expressly consent to the information handling practices described in this notice. 

This Privacy Policy applies to Twitch's collection and use of your personal information (i.e., information that identifies a specific person, such as full name, address, phone number, or email address). It also describes generally Twitch's practices for handling non-personal information (for example, interests, demographics and services usage). 

#### The Information Twitch Collects 

  * **User-provided Information** : You may provide to Twitch what is generally called "personal information" in the USA and elsewhere or "personal data" in the European Union (such as your name, email address, postal mailing address, home/mobile telephone number, credit card number and billing information) if you register for a Twitch Service, or upload, purchase, view or download certain content or products from the Twitch Service, enter contests or sweepstakes, or otherwise use the features and functionality of the Twitch Service. 

  * **"Cookies" Information** : When you access the Twitch Service, we may send one or more cookies - small text files containing a string of alphanumeric characters - to your computer. For information about what cookies are, how they work, how Twitch uses them and how to remove them, please see our cookie policy at [http://www.twitch.tv/user/legal?page=cookie_policy. ](http://www.twitch.tv/user/legal?page=cookie_policy)

  * **"Automatically Collected" Information** : When you access the Twitch Service or open one of our HTML emails, we may automatically record certain information from your system by using cookies and other types of tracking technologies. This "automatically collected" information may include Internet Protocol address (" **IP Address** "), a unique user ID, device type, device identifiers, browser types and language, referring and exit pages, platform type, version of software installed, system type, the content and pages that you access on the Twitch Service, the number of clicks, the amount of time spent on pages, the dates and times that you visit the Twitch Service, and other similar information. Depending on the law of your country of residence, your IP address may legally be considered personal information. 

  * **Information from Other Sources** : We may obtain information, including personal information, from third parties and sources other than the Twitch Service, such as advertisers or social media networks for which you have approved our access to information (e.g., information from your Facebook account provided by the Facebook APIs). When you access the Twitch Service through social media networks or when you connect a Twitch Service to social media networks, you are authorizing Twitch to collect, store and use such information and content in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We may also obtain information from third parties such as social entertainment platforms regarding your use of such services, including about your use of the content you choose to broadcast through the Twitch Service. If we combine or associate information from other sources with personal information that we collect through the Twitch Service, we will treat the combined information as personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy. 

#### The Way Twitch Uses Information 

  * Twitch uses the information that you provide or that we collect from or about you: to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features and services found on the Twitch Service; to improve your experience with the Twitch Service by delivering content which we hope you will find relevant and interesting, including advertising and marketing messages; to allow you to comment on content, and participate in online games, contests or rewards programs; and as necessary to comply as a service provider with the Digital Millennium Copyright Act or other similar legal obligations around the world. 

  * We will use your email address for administrative communications such as notifying you of major Twitch Service updates, for customer service purposes, to address copyright infringement or defamation issues, or to contact you regarding any content that you have posted to or downloaded from the Twitch Service. 

  * Twitch may periodically send promotional materials or notifications to you related to the Twitch Service. If you want to stop receiving promotional materials, you can go to [http://www.twitch.tv/settings ](http://www.twitch.tv/settings) once you have logged in to the Twitch Service or (for email) follow the unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email. If you have installed a mobile app and you wish to stop receiving push notifications, you can change the settings either on your mobile device or through the app. 

  * Twitch uses the information that we collect to understand the usage trends and preferences of our Users, to improve the way the Twitch Service works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. 

  * Twitch may use "Automatically Collected" information and "Cookies" information to maintain and improve the Twitch Service, including to do the following things: (a) automatically update the Twitch application on your system; (b) remember your information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you access the Twitch Service; (c) provide customized third-party advertisements, content and information; (d) monitor the effectiveness of third-party marketing campaigns; (e) monitor aggregate site usage metrics such as total number of visitors and pages accessed; and (f) track your entries, submissions, and status in any promotions or other activities. 

#### When Twitch Discloses Information 

  * Twitch does not share your personal information with other organizations for their own marketing or promotional uses without your prior express consent. Please be aware, however, that any personal information that you voluntarily choose to display on any publicly available portion of the Twitch Service - such as when you publish content, comments or profile information - becomes publicly available and may be collected and used by others. 

  * If you connect to a third party service (such as Facebook or Twitter) through an icon or link on the Twitch Service or otherwise link your Twitch account with a third party service, we may share the contents of your post and associated information (such as your user name, the fact that your connection originated from the Twitch Service, and other relevant usage and diagnostic information) with such third party.  With your one-time consent, we may also send information about the content you watch and your activities on the Twitch Service to such third parties. Once such information is shared, the use of your information will be subject to that service's privacy policy and this Privacy Policy will not apply. 

  * Twitch may disclose Automatically Collected and other aggregate non-personal information with interested third parties to assist such parties in understanding the usage and demographic patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, or other functionality of Twitch. 

  * Twitch may make both personal and non-personal information available to subsidiaries and affiliated companies that are under common ownership or control within the Twitch family. 

  * We may disclose both personal and non-personal information to service providers working on our behalf to: provide web site hosting, maintenance, and security services; fulfil orders; conduct data analysis and create reports; offer certain functionality; and assist Twitch in improving the Twitch Service and creating new services features. We require that these parties process such information in compliance with this Privacy Policy, we authorize them to use the information only for the purposes for which it is provided to them, and we require these parties to use reasonable confidentiality measures. 

  * Twitch may disclose User information if we believe in good faith that such disclosure is necessary to comply with US state and federal laws (such as U.S. Copyright law) or other applicable laws around the world (for example, in the country of your residence); or respond to a court order, judicial or other government subpoena, or warrant in the manner legally required by the requesting entity. 

  * Twitch also reserves the right to disclose User information that we believe, in good faith and after making reasonable enquiries, is appropriate or necessary to take precautions against liability to Twitch; protect Twitch from fraudulent, abusive, or unlawful uses; to investigate and defend ourselves against third-party claims or allegations to protect the security or integrity of the Twitch Service; or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of Twitch, our Users, or others. We will notify you of these disclosures if we reasonably think we can do so legally and without harming the purpose of the disclosure. 

#### Your Choices 

You may, of course, decline to share your personal information with Twitch, in which case Twitch will not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality found on the Twitch Service. If you would like to access, review, correct, update, suppress, or otherwise limit our use of your personal information you have previously provided directly to us, you may contact us as outlined in the last section of this Privacy Policy titled " **Twitch Contact Information** "; or using the mechanism provided below. In your request, please include your email address, name, address, and telephone number and specify clearly what information you would like to access, change, update, or suppress. We will try to comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable and any information you give us will be protected by this Privacy Policy. 

You may update, correct, or delete certain of your user information and preferences by visiting the [Settings Page ](http://www.twitch.tv/settings) once you have logged in to the Twitch Service. You may also request to update, correct, delete the personal information you have provided to us by contacting us at [privacy@twitch.tv. ](mailto:privacy@twitch.tv)

To protect your privacy and security, we take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting you account access or making corrections to your information. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique password and account information at all times. 

####  Advertisers and Analytics Providers 

We may use third-party Web analytics services on our site, such as those of Google Analytics and Mixpanel.  These service providers use a variety of tracking technologies such as cookies to analyze how users use the Twitch Service.  The information collected will be disclosed to or collected directly by these service providers, who use the information to evaluate your use of the Twitch Service.  To learn about opting out of Google Analytics, please  [click here. ](http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout) To opt out of Mixpanel, please [ click here. ](https://mixpanel.com/optout) Because these opt outs are cookie-based, please note that if you get a new computer or device, install a new browser, or erase or alter your browser's cookie file, you may need to opt out again. 

Twitch may allow advertisers, third-party advertising networks and third-party advertising serving companies to serve advertisements directly to you within the Twitch Service and other Twitch sites, services and software. By serving these advertisements directly to you, these companies can set their own cookies on your computer and trigger their own Web beacons and other tracking technologies to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements, and to collect and track information such as demographic information, inferred interests, aggregated information, and activity to assist them in personalizing the advertising content delivered to you. Twitch does not provide your personal information to these third-party ad servers or ad networks without your consent. However, please note that if an advertiser asks Twitch to show an advertisement to a certain audience (for example, males age 15 to 18) or audience segment (for example, males age 15 to 18 who have participated in certain promotions) and you respond to that advertisement, the advertiser or ad-server may conclude that you fit the description of the audience that they were trying to reach. 

This Privacy Policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the tracking technologies and activities of, those other advertisers, third-party advertising networks, or third-party advertising servers. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these advertisers, third-party advertising networks, or third-party advertising servers. For more information about third-party advertising networks and similar entities that use these technologies, see [http://www.aboutads.info/consumers ](http://www.aboutads.info/consumers) , and to opt-out of such ad networks' and services' advertising practices, go to the  [Network Advertising Initiative opt-out ](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/%29#completed) page, the [Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out ](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/) page, or the [Your Online Choices ](http://www.youronlinechoices.com/uk/your-ad-choices) page. 

Do Not Track ("DNT") is a privacy preference that users can set in certain web browsers. DNT is a way for users to inform websites and services that they do not want certain information about their webpage visits collected over time and across websites or online services. We are committed to providing you with meaningful choices about the information collected on our website for third party purposes, and that is why we provide the Network Advertising Initiative and the Digital Advertising Alliance opt-out links above. However, we do not recognize or respond to browser-initiated DNT signals, as the Internet industry is currently still working toward defining exactly what DNT means, what it means to comply with DNT, and a common approach to responding to DNT. 

#### Our Commitment to Data Security 

Twitch uses commercially reasonable physical, managerial, and technical measures designed to protect the integrity and security of your personal information. However, no security precautions or systems can be completely secure. We cannot therefore ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to Twitch, and you do so at your own risk. We cannot guarantee that such information may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. 

#### Our Commitment to Children's Privacy 

IF YOU ARE UNDER 13 YEARS OF AGE, THEN PLEASE DO NOT USE OR ACCESS THE TWITCH SERVICE AT ANY TIME OR IN ANY MANNER. 

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, Twitch does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from persons under 13 years-of-age. If Twitch learns that personal information of persons under 13-years-of-age has been collected on or through the Twitch Service, Twitch will take the appropriate steps to delete this information. 

If you are the parent or legal guardian of a child under 13 who has become a Twitch Service member, then please contact Twitch at [privacy@twitch.tv ](mailto:privacy@twitch.tv) to have that child's account terminated and information deleted. 

The following are some resources that may help parents and legal guardians in monitoring and limiting your children's' access to certain types of material on the Internet. While Twitch does not endorse these products, we provide information about them as a public service to our community. 

#### International Visitors 

For Users visiting the Twitch Service from the European Economic Area or other non-U.S. territories, please note that any data you enter into the Twitch Service will be transferred outside the European Economic Area or those other non-U.S. territories for use by Twitch and its affiliates for any of the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition, because Twitch operates globally, we may make information we gather available to worldwide business units and affiliates under the terms of this Privacy Policy. By providing any data on the Twitch Service, you hereby expressly consent to such transfers of your data to the United States or other countries, except in the case of data transfers from the European Economic Area or Switzerland, which are covered under our EU-US and Swiss-US Safe Harbor Certifications detailed below. For Users from outside the US, Switzerland or the European Economic Area, please note that laws in the US may not provide the same level of protection for information (which Users provide to Twitch or which Twitch collects from Users in connection with the Twitch Service) as the laws of the User's country of residence. 

Twitch complies with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Frameworks developed by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information from EU member countries and Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and view our certification on the U.S. Department of Commerce's Safe Harbor website, [click here. ](http://export.gov/safeharbor/)

In compliance with the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, Twitch commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. For all inquiries or complaints regarding this Privacy Policy, including European Union or Swiss citizens, should first contact Twitch by emailing [privacy@twitch.tv. ](mailto:privacy@twitch.tv) Twitch has further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-EU and US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles to an independent dispute resolution mechanism, the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR, operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed by Twitch, please visit the BBB EU SAFE HARBOR web site for more information and to file a complaint:  [BBB.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints. ](http://bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints)

#### In the Event of Merger or Sale 

In the event that Twitch or some or all assets related to the Twitch Service are acquired by or merged with a third-party entity, we reserve the right, in any of these circumstances, to transfer or assign the information that we have collected from Users as part of that merger, acquisition, sale, or other change of control. 

#### Changes and Updates to this Privacy Policy 

Twitch reserves the right to change, modify, add, or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time (for example to reflect updates to the Twitch Service or to reflect changes in the law). If Twitch changes this Privacy Policy, we will provide you notice of these changes, such as by sending an email, posting a notice on the Twitch Service, or updating the "Last Updated" date above. Please check this Privacy Policy periodically for those changes. Your continued use of the Twitch Service after the posting of changes constitutes your binding acceptance of such changes. For any material changes to this Privacy Policy, the amended terms will automatically be effective thirty days after they are initially posted on the Twitch Service and we will make reasonable efforts to provide you with choice regarding those changes, if required by law. 

#### Twitch Contact Information 

Please contact Twitch with any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy, your personal information, and our third-party disclosure practices or your consent choices at: 225 Bush Street, 6th Floor, San Francisco, CA 94104; by email: [privacy@twitch.tv ](mailto:privacy@twitch.tv) or by phone: 1-415-684-7494. We will respond to your inquiry within 30 days of its receipt. If you are a California resident, you may have this same information emailed to you by sending a letter to the foregoing address with your email address and a request for this information. 

#### Delete Account Data 

If you would like to delete all data associated with your account, go to <http://www.twitch.tv/user/delete_account>. This action is irreversible.
